上集成长的烦恼
Previously on growing pains:
迈克:你好,西维尔太太……难道你不愿意每天花费很少的钱去欧洲旅游来向你们的婚姻注入激情吗?
Mike: Hello, Mrs.Seaver...
Wouldn't you like to put the thrill back into your marriage by touring
Europe for just pennies a day?
麦琪:迈克,哪天你爸爸同意去欧洲旅游,
Maggie: Mike, the day your dad springs for a trip to Europe,
猪就能飞.
is the day pigs fly.
头等舱的座位?我从没想过.
Seats in first class?I had no idea.
迈克:不不不,伙计……你们的还没有到.是我的.
Mike: Nonono guys...this isn't your stop.It's mine.
开萝尔:迈克也去欧洲?
Carol: Mike is going to Europe too?
艾米:你有没有发现,根据线路,
Amy: Do you realize according to the itinerary we are not visiting the
我们不会去凭吊梵高的墓地.
grave of van Gogh?
迈克:身体健康.
Mike: Guzhuntait.
麦琪:嘿,瞧.艾菲尔铁塔.
Maggie: Hey look.The Eiffel tower.
哦,亲爱的,我想回到亨利饭店.
Oh, honey I want to go back to An-Rees
杰森:哦,是呀.
Jason: Oh yeah, so do I.
我也是.我们去哪里才能找到那么物美价廉的饭菜呢?
Where else can we get such great food at sensible prices?
麦琪:那儿也是你向我求婚的地方.
Maggie: It's also where you proposed to me.
艾米:你为什么来欧洲?
Amy: Why did you come to Europe?
迈克:我选择了一个地方,那儿6800万女人对我说的话一点不懂,
Mike: Well I figured a place with 68 million women who couldn't understand
也不是完全糟透了.
a word I said couldn't be all bad.
店主:你们的住宿凭证没有用,除非你们把它当作卫生纸.
Store Owner: Your vouchers are useless miss, unless you in need of toilet paper.(Spanish
艾米:这位是发发发疯公司的总裁.(西班牙语)
Amy: This man is president of vavava voom.(Spanish)
杰森:结婚纪念日快乐.
Jason: Happy anniversary.
麦琪:哦,杰森,喔--喔--
Maggie: Oh Jason, uuhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhhh
艾米:我们是被陷在欧洲了.我们有两张回程票,只有在巴黎有效,有效期六天.一个离我们500英里的城市.
Amy: I'm stranded in Europe.We have a pair of tickets that's good only in Paris in 6 days, a city 500 miles away
杰森:是阑尾炎,我们正送你去医院.
Jason: It's a appendicitis,
一切都会好的.
but we are taking you to the hospital everything is going to be fine.
迈克:如果我妈发现她可怜的儿子有困难,
Mike: When my mom finds out that her little boy is in trouble,
我可以感觉到她有多着急.
I can just hear her now.
麦琪:喔--喔--
Maggie: UUUHHHHH
杰森:哦,呼吸,亲爱的,呼吸,亲爱的.
Jason: Oh breathe honey, breath honey
麦琪:杰森,我们不是生小孩.
Maggie: Jason, we are not having a baby.
迈克:快来,快来……
Mike: Come on come on...
艾米:哦,行了,那里没人,不要那么哑口无言的.
Amy: Oh come on, nobody's there, don't be so dumb.
迈克:哑口无言?嘿!瞧,我又不是花光一生的储蓄来参加这次旅游.
Mike: Dumb?Hey look I'm not the one who blew her whole life's savings
我是免费来的.艾米?艾米,行了,你去哪里呀?
on this tour.I got it for free.Amy?Amy, come on where are you going?
艾米:巴黎.
Amy: Paris.
迈克:怎么去呀?
Mike: How?
艾米:我步行.
Amy: I'm walking.
迈克:靠腿?
Mike: By foot?
艾米:只是500英里,我有将近一周时间,
Amy: Its only 500 miles, I've almost got a week, I can do it.
我能做到.只要到处有饮料就行.
With a little beverage here and there.
迈克:哦,很好,
Mike: Oh well fine, well, who needs you,,
那么,谁需要你,你知道你将只会拖我后腿,
you know you will only slow me down,
而且你记住,我不该对你这么好.
and just for the record, 'm sorry I was so nice to you.
我不需要她,我会好起来的……可是我又没钱,
I don't need her, I'll be fine...
而且现在情况看起来不怎么好,该怎么办?
so what if I don't have a lot of money and things aren't looking so good
复水难收呀.先生?
right now?I've talked my way out of tougher jams.Sir?
先生:是我?
Sir: Si?
迈克:(西班牙语)巴黎在什么地方?
Mike: (In Spanish) where is Paris?
先生:法国.
Sir: France.
迈克:谢谢你.我在去那儿的路上.嘿,艾米,
Mike: Thank you.I am well on my way.Hey Amy, wait...
等等……瞧,我不能让你让你这样一个人走啊.嘿,停下来,你需要我.
look I can't let you travel alone like this.Hey wait up, you need me.
开萝尔:外婆,现在是凌晨两点……我还得坚持多久?
Carol: Grandma, It's 2 in the morning...how long do I have to keep this on?
外婆:这是密西西比河的瘀泥,
Grandma: Its Mississippi river mud dear...one minute to apply, an hour to dry.
亲爱的……敷只要一分钟,干要一小时.
It will suck the impurities right out of your skin...
By morning your face will be as soft as Benjamin's behind
开萝尔:这是令人作恶的比喻.
Carol: There's a disgusting image.
外婆:现在,你在沙发上休息,
Grandma: Now, you relax on the couch,
而我上去热一下电动镊子.
while I go up and warm up the power tweezers.
本:好呀,明天晚上老时间,
Ben: Yeah, same time tomorrow night stickman...
曲棍球手……我父母不在家,我可以逍遥法外.
with my parents gone, I can get away with murder.
(尖叫)
(Screams)
外婆:下面怎么回事?本杰米,
Grandma: What's going on down here?
你怎么到这个时候才回来,
Benjamin, what are you doing coming in at this hour?
干什么去了?你才9岁呀!
You are only nine years old.
本:我14岁了,外婆,我14了外婆,已经到了应征入伍的年龄了.
Ben: I'm fourteen grandma, old enough to be drafted.
外婆:哦,得了,那不同.开萝尔,
Grandma: Oh, well, that's different.Carol, you've never looked lovelier.
你从来没有这么漂亮过.就像巧克力布丁蛋糕,我明白了……
Into the chocolate pudding I see...
开萝尔:密西西比河里的瘀泥!
Carol: Its Mississippi river mud!
本:小子,你一定十分饥饿了.
Ben: Boy, you must have really been hungry.
外婆:嗨,嗨,嗨,嗨.
Grandma: Hey hey hey hey
本:满足我!
Ben: Get off of me!
外婆:安静.如果你把你外公吵醒的话……哦,
Grandma: Quiet.If you wake up your grandfather.....
也许敷一小时,干一分钟.
Oh, maybe it's an hour to apply, a minute to dry.
本:嘿,开萝尔已经成了一块石头了.
Ben: Hey Carol has turned into a stone.
开萝尔:什么?怎么回事?
Carol: What?What's going on?
外婆:现在,现在,
Grandma: Now now, it's nothing to be alarmed about,
没什么值得大惊小怪的,我马上把淤泥给弄掉.
I will have it off in a jiffy.
外婆:知道你爸爸把凿子放在哪儿了吗?
Grandma: Do you know where your father keeps his chisels?
开萝尔:迈克在西班牙,而我的脸冻结在淤泥里,不公平.
Carol: Mike's in Spain and my face is frozen in mud, its not fair.
巴士:早上好,现在开始销售去往北方所有地方的巴士车票.
BUS: Good morning, bus tickets are now on sale for all points north.
艾米:我们不是一道的.
Amy: We are not together.
迈克:哦,嗨,我说,谢谢把你的牙刷借给我.
Mike: Uh, hey say, thanks for lending me your tooth brush.
艾米:这不是你所想象的,昨晚我们睡在公园的长凳上.
Amy: Its not what you think, we slept on park benches last night.
不同的公园凳子,不同的公园.
Different park benches, different parks.
而且他没借我的牙刷,他偷的.
And he didn't borrow my toothbrush, he stole it.
迈克:我想他不说英语.
Mike: I don't think he speaks English.
开萝尔:很好,反正这一点也不关它的事.我能尽可能靠近巴黎的路程.(西班牙语)这是我所有的钱.
Carol: Good, it's none of his business anyway.Passage as far as I can go towards Paris.(Spanish) This is all the money I have.
迈克:是的,两张,
Mike: Yeah, 2, dos, me too.
我也是.嘿,我和你碰巧去一样的地方,
Hey can I help it if I happen to be going to the same place as
有什么办法?什么地方?
you are?Which is?
艾米:我可以告诉你,但是你仍然不会明白.
Amy: I could tell you, and you still wouldn't know.
迈克:啊,她通常就是这样……加拿大人.哦,嗨,
Mike: Ah, she's always like this...Canadian.Uh hey you say you don't need me?
你说你不需要我?嗨,听着,你需要我帮你保管车票.
Hey look, you need me just to keep your tickets straight.
艾米:那些不是车票,是钞票.
Amy: Those aren't tickets, that's money.
迈克:哦,那么我最好把它放在安全的地方.
Mike: Oh, well then I better keep this in a safe place.
艾米:这是我的钱,给我那……
Amy: It's my money, give me that...
迈克:嗨……
Mike: Hey.................
杰森:(西班牙语)怎么样了,医生?
Jason: (SPANISH) What's up doctor?
医生:啊,没必要说高中法语……
Doctor: Ah no need for the high school French...
杰森:我妻子怎么样了?
Jason: How's my wife?
医生:好极了,你有了个重四千克健康男孩.
Doctor: Excellent, and you have a 4000 gram healthy happy baby boy.
杰森:我听不明白.
Jason: I don't understand.
医生:啊,公制的……原谅我……你的儿子……他的体重是八磅.
Doctor: Ah, metric...forgive me...your son...he weighs eight pounds.
杰森:不,我们没有来生孩子.
Jason: No, I don't have a baby.
医生:当你孩子出生的时候你不在你妻子的身边就够坏的了,
Doctor: It is bad enough you are not by your wife's side when the child
现在你想完全否认她?
was born, now you disown her completely?
杰森:不,不……西维尔,
Jason: No, no..Seaver, my name is Seaver;
我姓西维尔;我带我妻子来切除阑尾的.
I brought my wife in here to have her appendix removed.
医生:哦,上帝.我们做了些什么……
Doctor: Oh sac le blue.What have we done...
杰森:你们做了些什么?
Jason: What have you done?
医生:哦,对不起,
Doctor: Oh, please, I'm sure it's just a little....how do you say....
我确信这只是小……你怎么说呢……病历混淆了.别担心;我一直都是会找不到病人的.
mix up in the paperwork.Don't worry; we loose patients all the time.
巴士:赶快,赶快,上车的最后通知.(西班牙语)
Bus: Hurry hurry, last call to re-board the bus.(Spanish)
迈克:听着,我不是想赶你,但是他们上车了.
Mike: Look, I don't mean to rush you but they are re-boarding the bus.
艾米:已经没有什么关系了.
Amy: It doesn't matter anymore.
迈克:嗨,如果你在数到三的时候,你不离开这地方的话,我就单独走了.1,
Mike: Hey if you are not out here by the count of three,
2,2.5,2.75……快点.
I'm leaving without you.
检票员:嗨,嗨,如果你们要上车的话,你们需要再买一张票.
Ticker man: Hey hey, if you want to get on you need to buy another ticket.
迈克:你说了什么,使得我们被踢下车?
Mike: What did you say to get us kicked off the bus?
艾米:我们的车票只能把我们带到这里.
Amy: Our tickets only took us this far.
迈克:那么,你告诉他们什么了?
Mike: Well, what did you tell him that for?
艾米:我没有告诉他,是他告诉我.满是灰尘,我讨厌灰尘.
Amy: I didn't tell him, he told me.Its dusty.I hate dust...
迈克:好了,那么我们可以再买车票呀.
Mike: All right look we can buy some more tickets.
艾米:我们没有钱了.
Amy: We don't have any more money.
迈克:哦,是吗?这是什么?
Mike: Oh yeah?What do you call this?
艾米:这是你的作废车票.
Amy: That's your cancel ticket.
迈克:你为什么对我发火?我们没钱,
Mike: What are you getting so mad at me for?
是因为我为我们俩买了午饭.
The only reason we don't have any more money is because I bought us lunch
艾米:你花了50美元买了那午饭.
Amy: You spent 50 dollars on a couple of ding dongs.
迈克:那么,他们没有提供与所给的钱等价值的食品,
Mike: well is it my fault that they don't put what the food is worth on
是我的错吗?嗨,你走那么快干什么?
the money?Hey, what are you walking so fast for?
艾米:距离巴黎还有400英里.
Amy: It's 400 miles to Paris.
迈克:400英里?我们还剩四天……那就是说每天70英里.
Mike: 400 miles?We got 4 days...that's 70 miles a day.
艾米:你真是个白痴.
Amy: You are such an idiot.
迈克:你说得对,你说得对……公里.
Mike: You are right, you're right...kilometers.
要比我们想象的要近.
We are even closer than we thought.
医生:恩,西维尔先生,你可以放松了.我们弄清楚了一切.
Doctor: Uh Mr.Seaver, you can relax.We straitened out everything.
杰森:我真希望这样.
Jason: I certainly hope so.
医生:这其实挺有趣.你瞧,
Doctor: It is actually quite amusing.
在西维尔太太,你的妻子,登记入院的同时,
You see, the same time that madam Seaver, your wife,
另外一个美国人,西蒙太太也正好登记入院.
checked into the hospital, another American madam Simon checked in too....
杰森:麦琪怎么样了?
Jason: How's Maggie?
医生:谁?
Doctor: Who?
杰森:我妻子,麦琪,她怎么样了?
Jason: My wife, Maggie, how is she?
医生:哦,哦,她正在手术,不要担心任何事情.
Doctor: Oh oh she is in surgery, don't worry about a thing.
护士:这是你的孩子,先生.(法语)
Nurse: Here is your baby sir (in French)
杰森:我更希望这是那段盲肠.
Jason: There better be an appendix in here.
艾米:谢谢你的鬼主意.
Amy: Thank for your help.
迈克:哦,快点,嗨,瞧,至少你可以做自己的本职工作.
Mike: Oh come on, hey look, at least you can do your part.
艾米:我不喜欢这样.
Amy: I don't like this
迈克:看起来就像孕妇……完美极了.
Mike: Just look like you are pregnant...perfect.
男人:我只能到这,我侄女今天结婚.(西班牙语)
Man: This is as far as I go, my niece is getting married today.(Spanish)
迈克:我们为什么停下来了?
Mike: Why are we stopping?
艾米:他也不喜欢你.他只能到这.
Amy: He doesn't like you either.This is as far as he goes.
迈克:恩,他准备把一个孕妇扔在这荒郊野岭?
Mike: Uh he's just going to leave a pregnant woman out here in the middle
那好;那我们自己来接生小孩吧.
of nowhere?That's fine; we will deliver the baby ourselves.
艾米:多谢.
Amy: Muchos gracias senior
迈克:是个儿子!!!
Mike: A son!!!
男人:疯狂的美国人!!!(西班牙语)
MAN: Locos americanos!!!(Spanish)
迈克:喔,你闻到了吗?
Mike: Wow, you smell that?
艾米:什么,什么呀;我正在走路.
Amy: Well, pardon me; I have been on the road.
迈克:不,不是你,好事.
Mike: No not you, something good.
嗨,过来,在那里,方向偏右,
Hey come on, its over here, a little off to the right,
大概100码.三大基本菜系.我闻得出来.
about 100 yards.3 of the basic food groups.I can smell them
艾米:哦,瞧,迈克……新娘……她真漂亮……哦,他们的衣服美极了……走吧……
Amy: Oh look mike....the bride....she's beautiful...oh their dresses are great....lets go
迈克:龙虾!!!
Mike: Lobster!!!
艾米:迈克,我是认真的.
Amy: Mike, I'm serious.
迈克:火腿!!!
Mike: Ham!!!
艾米:我们不想毁掉别人的婚礼.我不吃这食物……你不是想拿蛤蜊吗?
Amy: We are not going to crash someone's wedding.I'm not eating this food...
不,不是那个,是那个大的.
aren't you going to have any clams?No not that one, the big one.
男人:有什么需要帮忙的吗?
MAN: Can I help you?
艾米:走,迈克.
Amy: Let's go mike.
迈克:是,是,是,我们是美国亲戚.新郎的表兄弟.
Mike: Si, si si, we are American relativos.El cousins of the Groomo
艾米:我走了,迈克.
Amy: I'm leaving Mike.
迈克:我妻子刚生完小孩.
Mike: My wife just had a baby.
艾米:我没有生小孩,我生了个背包.
Amy: I did not, I had a knapsack...
迈克:快点,西班牙语里面的丈夫怎么说?
Mike: Quick, how do you say husband in Spanish?
艾米:Esposo. (丈夫)
Amy: Esposo.
迈克:我们是丈夫一方的……谢谢邀请我们来你家-哦.
Mike: We are with the esposo...Thank you for inviting us to your home-o
男人:小说谎者.为什么我不把他的脑袋像西瓜一样碾碎?
MAN: The little liar.Why don't we crush his skull like a melon?
迈克:他在说什么?
Mike: What's he saying?
艾米:他们喜欢你.
Amy: They like you.
迈克:好的,那么告诉他们,那个飞机丢了我们的礼物.
Mike: Ok well tell them the airlines lost our gift.
艾米:对不起.我们没有了钱,我们很饿,我们是美国人.是这样,我是美国人,他是加拿大人.对不起,哦,对不起.(西班牙语)
Amy: We are sorry.we have no money, we are hungry, we are Americans Well
I'm American, he's Canadian.Please, oh please.(SPANISH
男人:好吧,我不希望在我女儿结婚的日子见血.留下吧,吃你们想吃的.(西班牙语)
Man: Ok, there will be no blood spilled on my daughters wedding day.Please stay and eat all you wish (Spanish)
迈克:什么,什么呀?
Mike: What what?
艾米:他们邀请我们留下来吃.
Amy: They have invited us to stay and eat..
迈克:哈哈,谢谢,谢谢……我真疯狂,
Mike: Haha, gracias gracias...I'm crazy huh?
哈?我能把那小子饶在我手指上.什么?
I had that guy wrapped around my finger.What?
艾米:算了吧.
Amy: Never mind.
迈克:恩,艾米,我想我们最好跳舞去吧.
Mike: Uh, Amy, I think we better dance.
艾米:忘了?我不跳舞.
Amy: Forget it I don't dance.
迈克:你开玩笑,为什么不?
Mike: You are kidding, why not?
艾米:我不会跳舞,行了吧?
Amy: I don't dance ok?
迈克:为什么?
Mike: Why?
艾米:我从来就没有被这样追问过,但是没关系.
Amy: I haven't been asked that much, it doesn't matter anyway
迈克:好的,听着,我不是邀请你,我是告诉你……来吧.
Mike: Well look, I'm not asking you I'm telling you...come on.
艾米:迈克……
Amy: Mike...
迈克:右腿先,弯肘.
Mike: Right foot first, bend your elbow
电视机:气象预报,46华氏度,
TV: Today's forecast, 46 degrees with sleet on the way,
有时有雨加雪,奇妙的天气,
a bizarre day weather wise,
当欧洲每个城市均为多云和有雨,
as every European city is overcast and rainy except for Barcelona where
除了巴塞那气侯宜人,温度为82度.
it's a warm and beautiful 82.
开萝尔:我讨厌我的生活.
Carol: I hate my life
本:她说什么?
Ben: What did she say?
克莉丝:她说这不公平.她恨她的生活.
Chrissy: She said it's not fair.She hates her life.
本:听起来对我是一通胡言乱语.
Ben: Sounds like a bunch of gibberish to me.
克莉丝:永远是这样.
Chrissy: Same as always.
医生:你妻子好了,尽管这个星期她还得呆在医院里;她还感到有些疼痛.
Doctor: Your wife is fine,
although she will have to stay here for the rest of the week;
she is still in some pain.
杰森:但是你找对那个妇女了吧……金黄色头发,大概这么高,
Jason: But you found the right woman...
也许对目前状况十分恼火……
Blonde, about this tall, probably very cranky about now...
医生:就是她,没错.
Doctor: That's her all right.
杰森:那么她好吗,手术顺利吗?
Jason: So she's fine, the operation went well?
医生:哦,是,是,
Doctor: Oh yes yes, it went perfectly, no complications...
手术进行的很顺利,没有并发症……恩,就不必说的这么专业了……
uhm, without getting too technical...
杰森:没关系,我也是个医生……
Jason: It's alright, I'm a doctor too...
医生:哦,我没有意识到这点……那么你能理解我们的小混乱.
Doctor: Oh I didn't realize it...so you understand about our little screw-up.
杰森:不,不,
Jason: No no frankly I don't,
说实话,我不能理解,我从来没有见过管理这么差的医院.
I have never seen a hospital run quite this badly I'd be ashamed to practice
如果我在这里工作的话,会感到羞愧的.
in a place like this.
医生:你是什么专业的,西维尔医生?
Doctor: What is your specialty doctor Seaver?
杰森:精神病学.
Jason: Psychiatry.
医生:也许你可以把阑尾炎说掉.
Doctor: Perhaps you could have talked the appendix out.
杰森:亲爱的,这是你……
Jason: Honey it is you...
杰森:杰森.是男孩还是女孩?
Maggie: Jason.Is it a boy or a girl?
杰森:嘘……别让别人听到你说的.阑尾炎,
Jason: Shhh...don't let anyone hear you say that.
很快就会好了.
Its an appendix and you are going to be fine.
麦琪:哦,对了,我想起来了,我在医院里.
Maggie: Oh yes I remember, I'm in a hospital.
杰森:对呀.
Jason: Yes.
麦琪:在巴黎……
Maggie: In Paris...
杰森:你的气色好极了.我相信甚至你的伤口也可爱……耶,
Jason: And you look wonderful.I bet even your stitches are cute...
我说对了.
yeah, I was right.
麦琪:哦,杰森,怎么发生这样的事情?
Maggie: Oh Jason, why did this have to happen now?
杰森:嘿,差点更糟;我们差点再次成为父母.
Jason: Hey it could have been worse; we could have been parents again.
麦琪:啊?
Maggie: Uh?
杰森:说来话长.
Jason: Long story
麦琪:杰森,我们的结婚纪念日……我还得在这里多长时间?
Maggie: Jason, our anniversary...how long do I have to stay here?
杰森:这么,大概一周.
Jason: Well about a week.
麦琪:我们不能在安瑞宾馆里庆祝我们的结婚纪念了!
Maggie: We can't have our anniversary dinner at An Rees!
杰森:哦,你并没有毁掉任何事情.行了,我们在一起,我们在巴黎……恩?哇啦!
Jason: Oh, you know you haven't ruined a thing.Come on, we are together, we
are in Paris...uh?WALLA
迈克:哎,我告诉你什么问题使你烦恼……你只是不承认因为我的诡计多端,
Mike: Well, I'll tell you what's bothering you...
我们才有的吃.嘿,
you just can't admit that it was my cunning that got us fed.
你笑了!
Hey you are smiling!
瞧,我现在应该明白你在我翅膀下面有多幸运.
See, you do realize how lucky you are to be under my wing
艾米:是的,我确信.
Amy: Yeah, I sure do.
迈克:你知道我还能教你许多诡计……在你意识到之前,
Mike: You know there's a lot of tricks I can teach you...
你就结束了一段美好时光.
before you know it you'd wind up having a good time.
艾米:我说,我满足于不幸遭遇中的美好经历.
Amy: Let's say I settle for the best of a bad situation.
迈克:这很值得,艾米,你并不是你自己认为的那样无用.哦,我说的是真心话.嘿,瞧,能控制好这一切.
Mike: For what it's worth Amy, you are not the dud you think you are.Oh, and I mean that pretty much the way it sounds.Hey look, ill handle this one.
艾米:但是你不会说这种语言.
Amy: But you don't speak the language.
迈克:相信我,我不需要会外语.
Mike: Trust me, I don't need a language.
杰森:哦,给你枕头……这是我的.
Jason: Oh you got the pillow...that's for me
护士:……
Nurse: ...
杰森:不,你不理解我是为了她在这,
Jason: No you don't understand I'm here for her sake,
因此我愿意坐在这……瞧瞧你干了什么!对不起,
so I would be like to be sitting on something...Now look what you have done!
对不起……恩……发发疯公司,出去.
Excuse -a excuse-1 miss...uh...Va va voom, out!
麦琪:杰森,怎么回事?我花了两个小时才睡着.|
Maggie: Jason, what is going on?It took me nearly 2 hours to go to sleep.
这样,如果你还要坚持在这里,你能不能……
So if you are going to insist on staying here, would you please...
杰森:亲爱的,不要一再的感谢我了……我知道我在这对你意味着什么.
Jason: Honey no need for long thank you...
嘘!
I know what me being here means to you.Shhh
女人:就这了,路程结束了.(西班牙语)
Woman: This is it, end of the line.(Spanish)
迈克:谢谢,非常感谢.
Mike: Gracias, gracias a bunch.
艾米:我们这是在哪?
Amy: Where are we?
迈克:我们在巴黎,嗨,埃菲尔铁塔在哪里呀?
Mike: We are in Paris, hey where's the Eiffel tower?
艾米:我不相信!!你把我们带回我们的出发地了.
Amy: I don't believe this!!You brought us right back where we started.
迈克:哦,不,
Mike: Oh no I didn't,
我没有,我们离那个有人想杀我的宾馆有数英里.
we are miles away from that hotel was where that guy was trying to kill me.
艾米:他?
Amy: Him?
迈克:你去哪?
Mike: Where are you going?
艾米:离开你.我应该知道,那些智商比腰围还小的人,真是无用.
Amy: Away from you.I should have known that any guy whose IQ is less
than his waist size is useless
迈克:哦,行了,我可不是无用.
Mike: Oh come on I'm not useless.
艾米:那好,举个例子,
Amy: Ok, name one thing,
一件你做对的事情,自从落地西班牙以来.
just one thing that you got right since we landed in Spain.
迈克:好吧,我可不像你,我可没有把自己的钱包忘在车上.
Mike: Ok, well unlike you I did not leave my wallet in that truck.
艾米:啊!!!
Amy: Uhhhhhh!!!
迈克:我拿着,在这……你还能慢点?
Mike: I have it, right here...Would you slow down?
还有,
Of fine, you didn't thank me for the food,
你吃饭都没谢我,那么为什么要为钱包的事情谢我呢?
so why should you thank me for the wallet...
艾米:你没有弄到饭,是我.
Amy: You didn't get the food, I did.
那家伙要把你的脑袋像西瓜一样碾碎.
That guy was going to crush your cap like a melon.
迈克:怎么有人这么开他们自己的玩笑?
Mike: How can someone kid themselves like this?
听着,你能停一下吗?
Look, would you hold on a second?
我可以再次尝试联系我的父母.
Look, I can try to get in touch with my parents again.
艾米:行了,迈克,
Amy: Come on Mike,
我们两个都知道,指望父母是个大笑话.
we both know that this whole parent thing is just a big joke.
迈克:是的,我知道,但是至少他们有钱呀.
Mike: Yeah, I know, but at least they've got money.
我找杰森 西维尔医生?你说什么,
I'm calling for dr.Jason Seaver?What do you mean, he's checked out?
他已经付帐走了?没有去向地址?谢谢.
No forwarding address?Thank you.
艾米:按照我的计划路线,现在我应该在克比的小教堂里……我没说那是什么名胜古迹,
Amy: On my itinerary right now, I would be at this little church in Corbe...
我祖父母是在那儿结婚的.
I mean not like its any great landmark, my grandparents were married there
迈克:哎,瞧,
Mike: Yeah look can I borrow one of those little coins with the picture
你能否借一个有埃尔维斯头像的硬币给我?
of Elvis on it?
艾米:是胡安·卡洛斯国王.
Amy: That king Yuan-Carlos.
迈克:是的呀,瞧,在我书里,这里只有一个国王.
Mike: Yeah, look, in my book here is only one king.
艾米:因此现在你想要借走我最后的几个西班牙银币?
Amy: So now you want to borrow my very last pesetas?
迈克:谢谢……我想找到他们在哪里.
Mike: Thank you...I got to find out where they are.
克莉丝:我来接……四张红星,外婆.
Chrissy: I'll get it...Four hearts Grandma.
外婆:四张黑桃……
Grandma: Four spades...
克莉丝:你说大话,外婆……你在骗人.
Chrissy: Big talk grandma...you are bluffing.Hello?Chrissy Seaver's house.
喂?克莉丝 西维尔家.我爸爸告诉我不要接听对方付费电话.
My daddy told me not to accept collect calls.
迈克:克莉丝,我是迈克.
Mike: Chrissy, it's Mike.
克莉丝:好了,他说尤其是你打来的电话.
Chrissy: Hi, he said especially not from you.
迈克:那么你想怎么办,克莉丝?
Mike: So what are you going to do Chrissy?
克莉丝:我收取费用.
Chrissy: I accept the charges.
迈克:好你这个小女孩.
Mike: That a girl!
开萝尔:那是迈克吗?
Carol: Is that Mike?
克莉丝:不是,我的电话,而且是私人事情.出去.
Chrissy: No, it's for me, and it's private.Get out.
开萝尔:一定是迈克.
Carol: It is Mike.
克莉丝:好呀,开萝尔,你胆敢挂掉妈妈和爸爸的电话.
Chrissy: Nice Carol, you just hung up on mom and dad.
开萝尔:什么?
迈克:啊……她挂了……艾米?艾米?艾米?艾米?艾米?艾米?
00:22:12,300
Carol: What? Mike: UH...she hung up...Amy?Amy?Amy?Amy?Amy?Amy?